Ivanov Pavel

Front End Developer

grammka@gmail.com github.com/grammka linkedin.com/in/grammka

I have 6+ years experience in creating complex single-page applications as well as general website front-end. I know full web technology stack build process and how to make web apps faster. I have a solid experience in web design, which means that I can successfully handle projects that require professionals from two different fields - design and programming.

Technical Skill Set

	Technologies	Operating Systems	Other Technologies
•	HTML, CSS	• Linux	CoffeeScript, LiveScript
•	LESS, SASS, Stylus	UNIX	 Photoshop, Illustrator
•	JavaScript, AngularJs, React, Redux		• Git, SVN
•	Webpack, Gulp, Bower		• Ionic
•	E2E (Protractor)		

Professional Experience

HackPack Feb 2015 - Dec 2015

Startup. Journalism over the World (2700+ users)

Front-End Developer, Web-Designer, Co-Founder

- Was CTO of all client side parts. Communicated with users, community-development leads and the team. Made
 decisions for the development of usability.
- Designed and developed desktop version of site (hackpack.press). Created mobile version / application using lonic Framework
- Implemented multilanguage, E2E testing. Created awesome project structure with high speed building gulp process.

TerminalWMS Sep 2014 – Oct 2015

Front-End Developer

- Designed and developed highly loaded warehouse management system.
- Very complex project built on interdependent directives, services.
- Created my own nGrid library (10% AngularJS + 90% ES6).
- Implemented E2E testing (protractor)

BincSearch (Contract) May 2014 – Sep 2014

Front-End Developer

- Designed and developed Chrome extension for LinkedIn.
- Made some APIs in Django

Sociofactor Dec 2013 – May 2014

Front-end Developer

- Developed highly loaded projects for government agencies.
- Implemented E2E testing (protractor)
- Work on the project includes technologies such as: AngularJS, NodeJS, livescript, Jade

Mail.ru Group [Games] Jul 2013 - Dec 2013

Front-end Developer

- Created client side of new company website games.mail.ru
- Organizated structuring patterns, styles and scripts, perl-templating (Template Toolkit)
- Used stack of technologies (BEM + SASS, jQuery, Ajax)

Mail.ru Group [Search Engines]

Oct 2012 - Jul 2013

Front-End Developer

- Joined project in time team was planning to refactor full stack of site
- Refactored client side. Reworked css to SCSS + BEM. Cleaned JS and created modules.
- Developed versions for all platforms
- Added cross-browser compatibility (including IE6)
- Implemented BEM, SASS, worked with template engines ct++, Jinja, SVN, BEM

Biglion Sep 2011 – Oct 2012

Front-End Developer

- Created client side of new company website
- · Significantly improved my skills in jQuery, CSS3. Learned to work with Git, SVN

Goldenstudio Jul 2010 – Sep

2011

HTML-Coder, Junior Developer

- Significantly increased the level of knowledge of HTML-coding and programming (JavaScript, Perl, PHP).
- In conditions of constant shortage of time I have acquired the habit of working on the result.
- I engaged in web design. I participated in the development of new CMS (content management system) for the company.

Freelance 2008 – 2010

Was web designer

Education and Training

Education:

2009-2014 Moscow, HSE, web-designer